cruisercustomizing.com 2016-12-26

# Privacy Policy

This notice describes our Privacy Policy. By visiting cruisercustomizing.com ("[www.cruisercustomizing.com](http://www.cruisercustomizing.com/)", "Cruiser Customizing", the "Site", "we", or "us") you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Notice.

**1\. WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION DOES CRUISER CUSTOMIZING GATHER ABOUT ITS CUSTOMERS?**  
The information we receive from customers helps us personalize and improve your shopping experience at cruisercustomizing.com (the "Site"). Here are the types of information we gather:

Information You Give Us: We receive and store any information you enter on the Site or give us in any other way. You can choose not to provide certain information, but by doing so you may not be able to take advantage of certain features. We use the information you provide for such purposes as processing orders, assisting you with part fitment, responding to your requests, customizing your shopping experience, and communicating with you.

Automatic Information: We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. Like many websites, we use cookies and obtain certain types of information when you access the Site. Additionally, we utilize several Google Analytics products. Visitors may opt out of of these features through Google's opt-out browser, or other available methods.

Email Communications: If you make a purchase with us, or if you have otherwise elected to receive emails from us, we will not sell your email information. We send you emails to confirm orders, provide order status or notifications, for promotional purposes, and to communicate with you in general. To help us make emails more useful and interesting, we often receive a confirmation when you open email from Cruiser Customizing. We may also receive information regarding any "click-through" within the email, provided your computer supports such capabilities. If you no longer wish to receive email from us, you are allowed to unsubscribe from promotional emails.

In subscribing for a newsletter you agree that Cruiser Customizing (7419 Southfront Rd, Livermore, CA 94551) may use the data you entered to inform you by e-mail about the contents and/or products selected by you. You may revoke your consent at any time with effect for the future, either by written notice to Cruiser Customizing or by contacting us from our form here. You may also unsubscribe from any newsletter via the link provided at the end of each newsletter or call us at 1-888-857-5417.

**2\. WHAT ABOUT COOKIES?**  
Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive as a simple text string, through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and to provide features such as "Your Ride", "Your Garage", fitment data, personalized advertisements, and storage of items in your Shopping Cart between visits.

The Help portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. Additionally, you can disable or delete similar data used by browser add-ons, such as Flash cookies, by changing the add-on's settings or visiting the manufacturer website. However, because cookies allow you to take advantage of some of Cruiser Customizing's essential features, we recommend you leave them turned on. For instance, if you block or otherwise reject our cookies, you will not be able to add items to your Shopping Cart, proceed to Checkout, or use any of our products and services that require you to Sign in.

**3\. DOES CRUISER CUSTOMIZING SHARE THE INFORMATION IT RECEIVES?**  
Information about our customers is an important part of our business, and we are not in the business of selling it to others. We share customer information only as subject to this Privacy Notice.

Third-Party Service Providers: We employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include fulfilling orders, delivering packages, sending postal mail and email, removing repetitive information from customer lists, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, providing search results and links (including paid listings and links), and processing credit card payments. They have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes.

Promotional Offers: Sometimes we send offers to selected groups of Cruiser Customizing customers on behalf of other businesses, such as product distributors, vendors, and manufacturers. When we do this, we do not give that business your name or address. If you do not want to receive such offers, please unsubscribe from the email list.

Protection of Cruiser Customizing and Others: We release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law; enforce or apply our Site Terms and Conditions of Use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Cruiser Customizing, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. Obviously, however, this does not include selling, renting, sharing, or otherwise disclosing personally identifiable information from customers for commercial purposes in violation of the commitments set forth in this Privacy Notice.

With Your Consent: Other than as set out above, you will receive notice when information about you might go to third parties, and you will have an opportunity to choose not to share the information.

**4\. HOW SECURE IS THE INFORMATION ABOUT ME?**  
Your security is of utmost importance to Cruiser Customizing. We take every possible measure to ensure your personal information remains safe. These measures include:

-Data Encryption  
-Multiple Secure Sockets Layers (SSL) certifications  
-Payment Card Industry (PCI) Security Compliance  
-Secure Firewalls  
-Partnership with Authorize.net for Secure Payment processing  
-All transactions are protected by up to 256-bit Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) data encryption provided by GoDaddy.com  
-Premium Extended Validation (EV) SSL certification and Domain Secure Site validation by GoDaddy.com  
-Hacker, Spam, Malware, and Virus protection by SiteLock.com

We do NOT store your credit card information. We reveal only the last four digits of your credit card numbers when confirming an order. We transmit the entire credit card number to the appropriate credit card company during order processing.

Additionally, we recommend assigning a strong password to your account. It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your account. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer.

**5\. WHAT ABOUT LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES?**  
The Site may include links to other websites. Once you leave our Site, we no longer have access to, or control over cookies, information practices, or other features that third-parties may use. Therefore, third-party websites are not covered by this Privacy Notice. Please contact them directly for more information about their privacy practices.

**6\. WHICH INFORMATION CAN I ACCESS?**  
Cruiser Customizing gives you access to information about your account and your interactions with us for the limited purpose of viewing and, in certain cases, updating that information.

**7\. WHAT CHOICES DO I HAVE?**  
You can always choose not to provide information, although it might be needed to make a purchase or to take advantage of other Cruiser Customizing features. You can add or update your account information. When you update information, we may keep a copy of the prior version for our records.

If you do not want to receive email from us, please unsubscribe from the email list when you receive an email. (If you do not want to receive Conditions of Use and other legal notices from us, such as this Privacy Notice, those notices will still govern your use of the Site, and it is your responsibility to review them for changes.)

The Help portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. Additionally, you can disable or delete similar data used by browser add-ons, such as Flash cookies, by changing the add-on's settings or visiting the website of its manufacturer. However, because cookies allow you to take advantage of some of our essential features, we recommend that you leave them turned on.

**8\. ARE CHILDREN ALLOWED TO USE CRUISERCUSTOMIZING.COM?**  
Cruiser Customizing does not actively market to children, but does sell some products that are suitable for children, such as helmets, apparel, protective gear, toys, school supplies, stickers, etc. If you are under 18, you may use our Site only with the involvement of a parent or guardian.

**9\. SITE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF USE, NOTICES, AND REVISIONS**  
If you choose to visit the Site, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Notice and our Site Terms and Conditions of Use, including limitations on damages, resolution of disputes, and application of the law of the State of Indiana and California. If you have any concern about privacy at Cruiser Customizing, please contact us with a thorough description, and we will try to resolve it. Our Privacy Notice and the Conditions of Use may change over time as changes occur in our business and with our Site. We may email periodic reminders of our notices and conditions, unless you have instructed us not to, but you should check our Site frequently to see recent changes. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Notice applies to all information that we have about you and your account.

If you any questions or concerns please contact us or mail us at:  
Cruiser Customizing Customer Service  
7419 Southfront Rd.  
Building A  
Livermore, CA 94551

Go Back To Top

**<< Go Back To Customer Service**

Select your country to update currency & language. Select a country: Select display language: Reset
